An American Myth
The Man Who Killed Hitler and Then the Bigfoot is a drama,
adventure, fantasy film directed by Robert D. Krzykowski.
Decades after serving in WWII and assassinating Adolf Hitler, a legendary
American war veteran must now hunt down the fabled Bigfoot.
Calvin Barr, played by Sam Elliott.
Calvin Barr, played by Aidan Turner.
Maxine, played by Caitlin FitzGerald.
Maple Leaf, played by Rizwan Manji.
Ed, played by Larry Miller.
Flag Pin, played by Ron Livingston.
The Man Who Killed Hitler and Then the Bigfoot is a 2018 American adventure
drama film written, co-produced and directed by Robert D.
Krzykowski in his feature debut, and starring Sam Elliott, Aidan Turner,
Larry Miller, Ron Livingston, and Caitlin FitzGerald.
The film debuted at the Fantasia Film Festival in Montreal,
Quebec, where it premiered on July 20, 2018.
The US premiere took place at the Plaza Classic Film
Festival in El Paso, Texas on August 10, 2018.
In the UK, it played at FrightFest London on August 26, 2018, in Spain at the
Sitges Film Festival and in Finland at the Night Visions Film Festival.
The film explores themes of canada, war veteran, world war
ii, mythical creature, alternate history.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking.